Guide to the Peter Viereck papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VIII: Subject Files, 1935-2004
  - Andrei Tarkovsky's Film Andre Rublev--Notes, 1980s (Box 106)
  - Teaching Materials, 1942-1987 (Box 9, 34, 64, 67-68, 71, 73-74, 80, 91, 94)
  - Teaching Material for Poetry Workshops, 1965 (Box 36, 48)
  - Teaching Materials: Advice to Grad Student, undated (Box 44)
  - Theater, 1964-1976 (Box 106)
  - Thompson, Keith, 1954 (Box 112)
  - Traitors in Peacetime, undated (Box 112)
  - Transactions and Receipts, 2000s (Box 110)
  - Transcripts of "Enemy Broadcasts"--Analyzed by Peter Viereck While in the Psychological Warfare Branch--Issues of The Basic News, 1944-1945 (Box 71, 80)
  - Travel
    - Berkshires, 1990 (Box 108)
    - Boston, 1988 (Box 111)
    - Brandeis, 1988 (Box 111)
    - Cape Ann Area Addresses, undated (Box 108)
    - Clippings, 1993, undated (Box 108)
    - Correspondence--Multiple Countries, undated (Box 72-73, 92, 97)
    - Ralph Waldo Emerson Inn, circa 1995, undated (Box 108)
    - Hancock Area, 1970s undated (Box 108)
    - MacDowell Area, 1968-1998 (Box 108)
    - MacDowell Colony, 1981, undated (Box 108)
    - Magnolia, Massachusetts Clippings and Cards, 1982 (Box 108)
    - Massachusetts, 1992-1998 (Box 113)
    - Massachusetts Pamphlets, undated (Box 108)
    - Millay Colony Area, 1973-1991, undated (Box 108)
    - Miscellaneous Inns, 1989-1992 (Box 108)
    - New England Maps, undated (Box 108)
    - Restaurants, 1979, undated (Box 108)
    - Viereck's trip to Ralph Waldo Emerson Inn, 1997 (Box 108)
  - Tri Sources, 1964 (Box 106)
  - Trotsky, Leon--"I Stake My Life," undated (Box 106)
  - Tsarist and Soviet Life, 1965, undated (Box 106)
  - Under Discussion, 1964 (Box 110)
  - Undergraduate Notes, 1931-1936 (Box 68-69, 74-75)
  - Varoujan, Daniel--Speech Given by Peter Viereck on Varoujan, 1985 (Box 63)
  - Viereck Family Tree, undated (Box 106)
  - Viereck House, 1999 (Box 107)
  - Viereck Sign, undated (Box 108)
  - War Poems--Newspaper Clippings, 1940s (Box 103)
  - Wasserman--Interview, undated (Box 112)
  - Wheeler Notes, undated (Box 112)
  - Who's Who, 1987-1997 (Box 111)
  - Writing by Other People, undated (Box 110)
  - Writing Contest Information, 1994-2004 (Box 32-33, 47)
- Series IX: Personal Documents and Artifacts, 1933-1993
  This small series contains some of the Viereck family's personal documents such as address books, wills, educational records, death notices, and military records.
  - Account book, undated (Box 62)
  - Address Book, undated (Box 85)
  - Addresses, undated (Box 110-111)
  - Army Record, undated (Box 63)
  - Calendar, 1979 (Box 91)
  - Death Notice--George Slyvester Viereck, 1962 (Box 96)
  - French Honors Medal, undated (Box 62)
  - Honorary Diploma from Olivet College 1959 (Box 118)
  - Horace Mann Yearbook, 1933 (Box 80)
  - Travel Logs, 1960s undated (Box 105)
  - War Medal, undated (Box 83)
  - War Uniform--Badges (also for George Viereck Jr.), 1940s (Box 85)
  - Wills, 1979-1993 (Box 63, 83)
- Series X: Audiovisual Material, 1985-1997
  Series X is composed of various lectures and poetry readings on audio and video cassettes.
  - Architektur des Untangs--Videocassette, undated (2 cassettes) (Box 79)
  - Harvard Poetry Reading--Videocassette, 1997 November 14 (Box 79)
  - Last History Lecture--Videocassette, 1997 September 10 (Box 79)
  - Milosz Viereck--Audiocassette, 1985 October (Box 79)
  - Peter Viereck Reading His Poetry--Audiocassette 1992 February 7 (3 cassettes) (Box 79)
  - "Today's Revolts Against Communism in Eastern and Central Europe"--Audiocassette, 1990 February 7 (Box 79)
  - Unidentified Audiocassette, undated (Box 79)